fashionshopshoes.com 2015-12-10

# 

Administration of the Site (hereinafter "we", the "Site") recognizes the importance of confidentiality of personal information about Site users.

You can use the site without registering , but access to some sections of the site, such as My account, is possible only after registration. All personal information is provided only for the correct operation of the service.

We do not collect and process personal data, except those that have been provided voluntarily.

We collect and process personal data for the receipt and processing of orders, communication with customers for evaluation and planning of business processes, and to develop personalized offers for our customers.

Please be assured that your private data is not transmitted to third parties, and the administration of the Site shall take all possible measures to protect the data from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction.

Making payment you will be asked to enter the CVV or CVV2 code of your credit card. Do not worry. To protect your data we use the best technology in the Internet. Secure https address on the network shows that it is confidential. We use the security protocol SSL, which encrypts all personal and financial information. So you can be sure that we guarantee the highest level of security for each order that you make.

If you do not agree with the use of your personal data, please send a message to the Administration of the Site, which will contain your rejection of the use of personal data.
